Mission accomplished. Got the book done.
Writing a book is and was quite a lot
harder than I ever dreamed it to be.
So why did I do it? Why did I spend the
last year of my life working on weekends
late at nights to write this book?
What was behind it? Well, I'm
going to tell you real quickly.
You see, for 25 years now, I've had the
privilege and luck to have a career that I
really enjoy.
What I do is I'm a commercial real
estate manager, developer, and investor
specializing in commercial properties
in the South Florida market.
Now, I've loved this game for so long
and I've been through so many different
cycles of highs and lows,
from everything through pandemics and
recessions and banking crises to near zero
interest rates.
I've had the good and the bad. And overall,
this time, I've still loved what I've done.
And for me, I recognize that that's a gift.
So as my career grew and as our company
Current Capital grew, we started trying to
help more people come into this arena as
buying real estate and learning the game,
whether it's learning how to lease and manage
properties or invest in our own property.
You see, I've loved it so much, I find
that giving back is very rewarding.
So a couple of years ago, our company Current
Capital, we started bringing on interns.
And we brought on these young high school
and college kids in the summer, paid
internships, and we taught them real estate.
And I really got excited about this because
I said these young kids are looking at
their future with so much time to go.
And they're realizing that they could
invest in real estate at a young age and
there's nothing better
than time in real estate.
From there, I said I want to do more. So
I started answering the calls and started
doing a lot of guest posts on podcasts.
And I was giving time and doing all the
podcasts and reaching a lot of people.
And at the end of every podcast, I'd
always offer up my phone number, email and
said, if I didn't explain something
or you have more questions, call me.
And people did. And they were always
surprised that I would take their calls.
And I loved helping them and hearing people
buy their first or 15th property with
any help from me and my
experience was very rewarding.
So we kept on giving back more. At that
point, I said, how could I reach an even
bigger audience because I
really love helping people.
And that's where the book came from. Keeping
It Real on Commercial Real Estate. And
I'm going to keep it real.
You see, I don't have a program to sell.
I'm not going to tell you at the end of
the book that you need to join my mastermind
course or my mentoring coaching program.
I don't have that. I don't do it. It's not
available. I help for free because truthfully,
the more I help, I found that
I become better at my own game.
You see, if I'm going to tell you how to
do it, I better keep my standards high. So
there is something in it for me, too.
But giving back has been so rewarding
that this book is what I did.
Now, to be sure you, the reader, understand
that I wrote this book for you and it's
a conversation for you.
And in these 200 pages, I'm going to
teach you everything and investing in real
estate from what the good is, what the bad is.
And I'm going to tell you the
truth. I'm going to keep it real.
You see, it's not always about collecting
a rent check on the first of the month
and cashing out when you refi.
It's also about dealing with roofs that
cave in, fires, hurricanes, you name it.
There is good and there's bad.
So I'm going to give you the truth of both
sides. Maybe you don't want to invest in
real estate of your own.
Maybe what you'd like to do is
invest in a publicly traded company.
I'm going to tell you how to do that,
too, because I believe there's no better
asset class to put your investment dollars
in for you and your family's future than
commercial real estate.
And I think you'll agree in reading
this book that my intentions are there.
But to show you how authentic my intentions
are, I decided to take it one step further.
See, I wrote this book. I put it all
together and I picked up all the cost.
What I'm also going to do is give away
100 percent of the proceeds to charity.
So there is nothing in this book for me.
Again, I don't have a program at the end
to sell you. I'm not asking you to buy
anything or do anything with me.
I'm saying you buy this book. You're
going to learn a lot about real estate.
You're going to really be educated on
different classes of real estate, whether it's
a multifamily property, a warehouse, an
office building, or whether, like I said,
you want to buy stock in Public Storage.
I'm going to tell you the difference
in what you could expect from each.
And then all the proceeds from this
book I'm going to give to charity.
So it's a win-win situation.
And for all the parents watching, all the
parents of teenagers in high school and
college, your 18-year-olds, your 25-year-olds,
even your 30- and 40-year-olds, I
don't care, but the young people.
You must read this book or books like this
because, you see, you have the greatest
tool in time.
The other day I was sitting with a
30-year-old who was about to buy his first
multifamily property.
And I was jealous of him saying, my God,
this kid, I'm going to be 50 in a month.
This guy's got 20 years to
do this and play this game.
He buys one property at 30
and never does anything again.
He could retire off it and live the
rest of his life comfortably off of one
property because he's making a decision at 30.
Imagine what you do when I'm talking to
18-year-olds who are excited about buying
their first deal.
It's super rewarding.
I had the privilege of buying my first
property at 25 years old. I'm almost 50.
I still own that property today.
Now, it's worked out very well for me, and
that's why I want to give you the truth
in real estate.
I want to keep it real, and I want you to
buy my book, help make it a bestseller.
Learn something, enjoy it,
share it with your friends.
And when you love it, which I know you're
going to love it, write a good review.
So those people who don't know me can go
online and recognize it and buy it as well.
Thank you.